## SHIRLEY KAFFREY

### Shirley.Kaffrey@gmail.com

### Summary

Web Developer knowledgeable in React, javascript, CSS, version control and IDE. Stellar customer service record and superb work ethic. Prior work experience in Healthcare as a manager, meeting productivity standards and interpersonal communication. To be part of a team that provides quality client support in a culture of innovation, collaboration and technical advancement.

#### **Skills**

- React, Javascript, HTML and GIT
- Creative Problem Solver
- Attention to Details

- Adept at communicating efficiently and effectively
- Collaboration

### Portfolio, Profile, GitHub

- https://shirleyk.herokuapp.com/
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/shirley-k-59835b158/
- https://github.com/Sjazfrey

### **Experience**

# Software Developer Internship Queen's Web

01/2021 to present Remote

Frontend React developer who's responsibilities includes implementing designs from Figma to create an Enterprise level application similar to Groupon.

### **Software Developer Student**

05/2020 to 08/2020

### **General Assembly Software Engineering Immersive Program:**

Remote

Applied skills in CRUD apps, Git, GitHub, DOM manipulation, AJAX, NodeJS, HTML, React, Javascript, CSS, jQuery, Express, 7 RESTful routes, MongoDB and Mongoose, Group Project, Sessions and Authentication, along with Heroku. Developed 4 projects utilizing the above mentioned skills and technologies.

# Rehab Director / Physical Therapist Assistant Legacy Healthcare

04/2014 to 03/2020

Longmont, Colorado

As Rehab Director my responsibilities include directing the growth and development of the rehab program, effective collaborative communication with the patients, family members, vendors, and physicians.

Additionally, as a Physical Therapist Assistant I am proficient in all competency areas including patient care, communication with the Physical Therapist, program development, documentation, therapy software responsibilities and patient rights and safety.

#### **Education and Training**

Software Developer
General Assembly
Remote

Associate of Applied Science: Physical Therapy

Colby Community College